<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">

    <string name="app_name">EP Coding</string>
    <string name="title_procedure_detail">Coding</string>
    <string name="save_code_selection_title">Save</string>
    <string name="settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="about_title">About</string>
    <string name="about_label">EP Coding</string>
    <string name="about_text">Copyright \u00a9 2013 - 2017 EP Studios, Inc.
		\nAll rights reserved.\n</string>
    <string name="help_title">Help</string>
    <string name="search_title">Search</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search codes</string>
    <string name="primary_codes_label">Primary Code(s)</string>
    <string name="add_on_codes_label">Additional Code(s)</string>
    <string name="coding_summary_label">Summarize</string>
    <string name="coding_summary_dialog_label">Summary</string>
    <string name="clear_label">Clear</string>
    <string name="empty_message"/>
    <string name="no_codes_selected_label">No codes selected.</string>
    <string name="no_primary_codes_message">No primary codes.</string>
    <string name="no_primary_codes_verbose_message">You shouldn\'t just have additional codes.</string>
    <string name="no_secondary_codes_message">No additional codes selected.</string>
    <string name="no_secondary_codes_verbose_message">Be certain there aren\'t other codes that you are overlooking.</string>
    <string name="all_addons_error_message">All codes are add-on codes.</string>
    <string name="all_addons_verbose_error_message">Add-on codes must only be added to regular codes.</string>
    <string name="no_mapping_codes_message">No mapping codes for ablation.</string>
    <string name="no_mapping_codes_verbose_message">You should be able to code 2D or 3D mapping for this kind of ablation.</string>
    <string name="unassigned_sedation_message">No sedation codes.</string>
    <string name="unassigned_sedation_verbose_message">Did you supervise sedation? Sedation codes
    are no longer bundled with the procedure codes.</string>
    <string name="no_sedation_used_message">Procedure was performed without sedation</string>
    <string name="short_sedation_time_message">No sedation codes as sedation time was &lt; 10 minutes.</string>
    <string name="sedation_other_md_message">Sedation performed by other MD.</string>
    <string name="sedation_other_md_verbose_message">Procedural MD should not submit sedation coding. Sedation coding must be submitted by other MD</string>
    <string name="afb_ablation_help_text">AFB ablation includes comprehensive EP testing, including LA
	    recording and pacing.  It also includes transseptal
	    catheterization, therefore these codes cannot be added on.
	    Mapping codes and coding for programmed stimulation after IV drug infusion can be
	    added.  The primary code includes pulmonary vein isolation.  Add
	    code 93657 if additional ablation for AFB is done (such as linear
	    atrial ablation) and add 93655 if a separate arrhythmia mechanism
	    is ablated (such as focal atrial tachycardia).</string>
    <string name="av_node_ablation_help_text">It is not clear if electrophysiologic testing and mapping can be
	    billed as additional codes to AV node ablation.  Often AV node
	    ablation is combined with device implant at the same setting and
	    these codes should be added.</string>
    <string name="svt_ablation_help_text">SVT ablation includes comprehensive EP testing, but can be
	    combined with the other codes listed.  Note that the SVT ablation
	    code (93653) is used not just for supraventricular tachycardia,
	    but for WPW ablation, atrial flutter ablation, atrial tachycardia
	    ablation, and presumably premature atrial complex ablation.  If
	    more than one arrhythmia mechanism is ablated, add code 93655.</string>
    <string name="vt_ablation_help_text">VT ablation includes comprehensive EP
        testing.  Mapping codes (93609 or 93613), for reasons only known to the
	    AMA, cannot be combined with the 93654 VT ablation code.
	    This is unlike the AFB and SVT ablation codes.  LV pacing and
	    recording also cannot be combined with VT ablation.</string>
    <string name="ep_testing_help_text">The most commonly used codes for EP testing is 
        93620.  EP testing is not coded separately if ablation is performed.
	    Mapping can be added to EP testing codes, as well as LA pacing and
	    recording, programmed stimulation after IV drug, etc.  The two
	    primary codes lists are the most commonly used, other rarely used
	    codes, such as His bundle recording only (93600) are listed in
	    the All EP Codes module, but probably should be avoided.</string>
    <string name="devices_help_text">Temp device procedures help text</string>
    <string name="new_ppm_help_text">These codes are used for implantation of a pacemaker
        generator and lead(s).  Use the code that corresponds to the lead(s) put in.
        Use 33208 and 33225 for implantation of a pacemaker with CRT (i.e. with a
        coronary sinus lead).  These codes are also used when there is removal of 
        a prior system (generator and leads) and replacement with new generator and
        leads.  Do not use these codes for simple generator replacements.</string>
    <string name="new_icd_help_text">A new single or dual chamber ICD with new leads 
        is coded with the same code, 33249.  Code 33225 is added to 33249 if an
        LV/coronary sinus lead is added.  Use 93641 for DFT testing at the time
        of the implant.  These codes are also used if an ICD system (generator and
        leads) is removed and replaced with a new generator and leads.  Do not
        use these codes for simple generator replacement.</string>
    <string name="icd_replacement_help_text">These codes are used for ICD generator
        replacement only.  Use the primary code that is specific to the type
        of generator being replaced.  Do not use these codes for system revisions or
        upgrades.  A common additional code is 93641 for DFT testing during the
        procedure.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_device_help_text">This module contains a grab-bag of codes,
        and these procedures are definitely the most difficult to code.  If you are
        just replacing a generator, use the Replace ICD or Replace PPM modules.  If
        you are upgrading devices, changing from PPMs to ICDs, adding leads,
        extracting leads, removing generators without replacement, this module
        should have the codes you need.  The basic principle to follow is to
        use specific codes for what you are removing (leads or generators) and then
        use codes for new complete systems.  Example - upgrade dual chamber PPM or
        ICD with CRT, old leads left in place: 33233 (removal of PPM generator only),
        33249 (insert single or dual chamber ICD with leads), and 33225 (add coronary
        sinus lead).  However there is a code (33214) to upgrade a single chamber to
        a dual chamber PPM.  Example - upgrade single chamber PPM to PPM
        with CRT: 33214 (upgrade single to dual chamber PPM, includes new lead) and
        33225 (add CS lead).  Finally here is upgrade of single chamber ICD to ICD
        with CRT: 33249 (Insert new/replacement ICD with single or dual leads), 33225
        (add CS lead) and 33241 (removal of ICD generator only).  If you are
        unsure how to code something, check with your coders.</string>
    <string name="all_codes_help_text">As an alternative to using the procedure 
        oriented choices in EP
	    Coding, the All EP Codes module allows you to pick any of the codes in
	    any combination.  This may be useful if you are doing something
	    unusual that is not covered in the other procedure lists, or if
	    you are very familiar with how to use the codes and just want to
	    select from the complete list.  The list is ordered by code number.
	    By default there is NO analysis of coding in
	    this list, though this can be turned on in Settings.  It is possible to enter 
	    combinations of codes that
	    conflict.  As always, with increased freedom comes increased risk.</string>
    <string name="other_procedure_help_text">These are miscellaneous EP procedures
        and their coding is quite straightforward.  Just pick the code(s) you need.</string>
    <string name="subq_icd_help_text">SubQ ICD codes are new and will probably
        be changed as the procedure becomes established.  There are no real
        guidelines yet for using these codes.  These codes are not checked for
        consistency when you summarize them.</string>
    <string name="afb_ablation_title">AFB Ablation</string>
    <string name="svt_ablation_title">SVT Ablation</string>
    <string name="vt_ablation_title">VT Ablation</string>
    <string name="avn_ablation_title">AV Node Ablation</string>
    <string name="ep_testing_title">EP Testing</string>
    <string name="ppm_replacement_title">Replace PPM</string>
    <string name="other_procedure_title">Other Procedure</string>
    <string name="all_codes_title">All EP Codes</string>
    <string name="all_codes_primary_title">All EP Procedure Codes</string>
    <string name="save_code_selection_error_message">First select a procedure</string>
    <string name="no_secondary_codes_error_message">Only additional codes can be saved. This group has only primary codes.</string>
    <string name="no_code_errors_message">No errors or warnings.</string>
    <string name="no_code_analysis_performed_message">No code analysis performed in this module.</string>
    <string name="show_add_on_plus_label">Distinguish add-on codes</string>
    <string name="show_add_on_plus_on_summary">Add-on codes have +</string>
    <string name="show_add_on_plus_off_summary">Add-on codes don\'t have +</string>
    <string name="show_code_details_label">Show descriptions</string>
    <string name="show_code_details_on_summary">Show codes and descriptions</string>
    <string name="show_code_details_off_summary">Show codes only</string>
    <string name="truncate_code_descriptions_label">Truncate descriptions</string>
    <string name="truncate_code_descriptions_summary">Long descriptions can clutter screen</string>
    <string name="code_analysis_verbosity_label">Code analysis detail</string>
    <string name="show_plus_code_summary_key">show_plus_code_summary</string>
    <string name="code_check_all_codes_key">code_check_all_codes</string>
    <string name="show_details_code_summary_key">show_details_code_summary</string>
    <string name="truncate_long_descriptions_code_summary_key">truncate_long_descriptions_code_summary</string>
    <string name="code_check_all_codes_summary">Perform analysis in All EP Codes module</string>
    <string name="code_check_all_codes_label">Check codes in All EP Codes</string>
    <string name="code_verbosity_key">code_verbosity</string>
    <string name="subq_icd_title">SubQ ICD</string>
    <string name="new_ppm_title">New PPM</string>
    <string name="new_icd_title">New ICD</string>
    <string name="icd_replacement_title">Replace ICD</string>
    <string name="device_upgrade_title">Upgrade/Revision/Extraction</string>
    <string name="wizard_test_text">Test text for the Coding Wizard.</string>
    <string name="title_template_step">Step <xliff:g id="step_number">%1$d</xliff:g>: Device
        Wizard</string>
    <string name="action_previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="action_next">Next</string>
    <string name="action_finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="wizard_title">Device Wizard</string>
    <string name="slide_step1_heading_text">Is this a new implant or simple generator
        replacement? If so exit this wizard by using the back button on your device and
        go directly to the appropriate module (e.g. New PPM, New ICD, Replace PPM,
        or Replace ICD). Otherwise go to next step.</string>
    <string name="slide_step2_heading_text">Is this an upgrade from a single to
        a dual chamber pacemaker?  If so use code 33214 which covers this entire procedure.
        If you are also adding an LV cardiac vein lead add code +33225.
        Exit the wizard by using the back button
        on your device and select codes from the Upgrade/Revision/Extraction module.
        Otherwise go to the next step.</string>
    <string name="slide_step2a_heading_text">So we don\'t forget, add sedation coding now.</string>
    <string name="slide_step3_heading_text">Is this a lead revision or repair or a pocket revision
        without adding or removing any hardware?  If so use one of the codes below and
        then skip forward to the final page of this wizard.  Otherwise
        go on to the next step.</string>
    <string name="slide_step4_heading_text">OK. We have addressed the simple scenarios.
        What\'s left are lead and generator removals/extractions,
        and device upgrades. Start off by selecting what hardware (if any) was
        removed, and then go to the next step.</string>
    <string name="slide_step5_heading_text">Now if you added any hardware, code what you added.
        If you added a generator and leads, use the new or replacement system codes (e.g. new single
        chamber PPM).  If you just added a lead or a generator, code for the specific device(s) you
        added.  Then go to the next step.</string>
    <string name="slide_step6_heading_text">Did you do anything else? If so select from the choices
   	    below. Select Finish to see a summary of your codes.</string>
    <string name="no_data_label">No matches found!</string>
    <string name="default_verbosity">Verbose</string>
    <string name="sedation_button_label">Sedation</string>
    <string name="modifiers_label">Modifiers</string>
    <string name="add_label">Add</string>
    <string name="save_label">Save</string>
    <string name="reset_button_label">Reset</string>
    <string name="cancel_button_label">Cancel</string>
    <string name="add_sedation_button_label">Add Sedation</string>
    <string name="calculate_sedation_time_button_label">Calculate</string>
    <string name="no_sedation_button_label">No Sedation</string>
    <string name="patient_more_than_5_button_label"><![CDATA[Patient > 5 y/o]]></string>
    <string name="sedation_time_label">Sedation Time (min)</string>
    <string name="sedation_by_same_md_label">Sedation by Same MD</string>
    <string name="sedation_time_hint">Sedation time in minutes</string>
    <string name="finish_date_time_label">Finish Time</string>
    <string name="start_date_time_label">Start Time</string>
    <string name="sedation_label">Sedation</string>
    <string name="sedation_time_calculator_label">Sedation Time Calculator</string>
    <string name="set_button_label">Set</string>
    <string name="use_unicode_symbols_key">use_unicode_symbols_key</string>
    <string name="use_unicode_symbols_summary">Not all devices support Unicode fonts</string>
    <string name="use_unicode_symbols_label">Use Unicode error symbols</string>
    <string name="verbose_label">Verbose</string>
    <string name="version">Version %s</string>


</resources>
